Contact

+917905185813 (Mobile) rajivnayanc@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rajivnayanc (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C++

С

HTML

Languages

English (Full Professional) Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Front-End Web Development with React

Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4

Build a Modern Computer from First Principles: Hardware

PadhAl -Deep Learning Course

Server-side Development with NodeJS, Express and MongoDB

Publications

Internet Traffic Classifier Using Artificial Neural Network 1D-CNN

Rajiv Nayan Choubey

Deep Learning Enthusiast | Ex-Summer Intern (SDE) at Goldman Sachs | Full Stack Developer

Raipur

Summary

I am a currently pursuing B.Tech(CSE) at IIIT-Naya Raipur. I am a Web developer. I have also worked on AI and ML small-scale projects. Good at competitive coding too. I have cleared preliminary online round of ACM-ICPC 2018 and got selected for ACM-ICPC 2018 onsite round in Kolkata.

Experience

Campus Adda

Co-founder and Technical Head November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Raipur Area, India

A small startup by group of four members of IIIT-NR. Here, we sell hoodies and T-shirts to college students.

The Society of Coders, IIIT-NR Co-Founder

May 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Naya Raipur

The Society of Coders is technical coding, programming and development club of IIIT-Naya Raipur

Goldman Sachs Summer Intern (SDE) May 2020 - June 2020 (2 months)

E-Cell, IIIT-Naya Raipur Head of Startup Development October 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 1 month) Raipur Area, India

Education

International Institute of Information Technology, Naya Raipur Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Glenhill School, Varanasi Intermediate, PCM